VERITY GRISCTI

UX DESIGNER

I'm a diligent UX Designer who's concerned about every stage of the design process. I have worked in a variety of areas including, content management, marketing and web development, and this background informs my current design practice.

SKILLS

General:

Information Architecture
Digital Product Design
Rapid Prototyping
User Research
User Testing
Writing
W3C Accessibility Standards
Content Management

Design:

Figma
Typography
2D Design
Colour Theory

Engineering:

HTML5/CSS3/JavaScript Git & Git Hub Command Line VS Code

CONTACT

647.705.1234 verity.griscti@gmail.com www.veritygriscti.com

GitHub: @veritygriscti LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/veritygriscti/

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

UX/UI Designer

Freelance (April 2021 - Present)

I work with Small Business Owners to develop intuitive digital products and online experiences. I have re-designed existing web pages, designed brand new Apps, and have created Landing Pages from the content outwards.

Manager of Communications & Special Projects

Akimbo Art Promotions (2019 - 2020)

Managed and monitored day to day activity across all Akimbo's social media channels. Approximately 30,000 followers across Facebook, Twitter & Instagram.

Designed and built "Beyond the Biennial", a suite of navigation tools to aid tourists visiting Toronto's 200+ visual art venues during the 2019 Toronto Biennial of Art.

Digital Marketing Specialist

Mysteriously Yours Dinner Theatre (2015 - 2020)

Created, curated and maintained all written and visual content for the theatre's website and social media channels.

- Organically increased the total number of followers by 100% across all Social Media Channels.
- Secured inclusion in posts on high traffic sites: The Food Network, The Culture Trip and Indie88.
- Produced successful cross-promotional contests and giveaways with business partners in the retail and publishing industries.

Project Manager - Gallery Tours

Akimbo Art Promotions (2012)

Coordinated with Akimbo's Director, web design and development team and 6 writers to develop a database of 31 art focused walking tours across 6 Canadian cities.

Web Content Specialist

Akimbo Art Promotions (2007 - 2011)

- Constructed, published and maintained all web content for the company's high traffic website.
- Designed and constructed e-Newsletters for 10,000+ subscriber base.
- Provided customer service via email and phone to 200+ clients.
- Incorporated PayPal buttons on the websites payment page.

EDUCATION

UX Design, Certificate

York University School of Continuing Studies, 2021

Computer Programming Applications, Certificate

Ryerson University -

G. Raymond Chang School of Continuing Studies, 2020

B.F.A - Visual Arts

OCAD University, 2004

ONLINE CERTIFICATIONS

WAIO.1x: Introduction to Web Accessibility

W3Cx, 2020

Accessibility for Ontarians with Disabilities Act (AODA)

OSG, 2020

Google Analytics for Beginners

Google, 2020

AWARDS & ACHIEVEMENTS

Award of Excellence for Website Design

Heritage Toronto

For the Biographical Dictionary of Architects in Canada 1800-1950 [Project Director & Editor - Robert G. Hill].